Today I have an agency in Italy, we are
40 people who answer emails,
make calls, write creators,
negotiate contracts, give
presentations.  Then when I come here to
Sic with Valley and they tell me that a single
entrene with five agents does all
this alone, I ask myself ok, how can I
transform the power of this team of
40 people into a team of 400?
The best thing you can do is go
to Replit because you're talking to me,
so you have to hear my shameless
plug.  Work on it for a day, act
like you're one of them, and then have a
meeting with your entire company and
show them what you managed to do in
a day using that product.  If it
comes from the CEO, if it comes from leadership it
completely changes the perspective.
In my opinion, you find yourself going from a company of
40 to 200 people in the space of a few
weeks.
What are the tasks that could
most benefit from being
automated?  Usually the
most striking success stories are those of
Ampoli who have very
repetitive workflows, there is no tool to
solve them, they build something
internally and suddenly everyone
in the company uses it.  The same
thing happens to replet.  I'll tell you a very
banal one.  Every time you sell
an enterprise product to a company, you must create an
order form.  There are many people who
customize the order form depending on
what they need.  They have to do everything
manually, they send emails, they receive the
version with the signature, until
someone inside has decided, you know what?
Now I'm disappearing for a week, I'm
making a tool on Repit that
automatically generates the order form based on
four metadata that you pass it.  Suddenly
no one thinks about the former Rapid anymore and
she has become a
deal desk person, she has almost become a
software engineer part despite
having never written a single piece of code in
her life and she is super proud of it as is
right because she has made the
sales team much more efficient than it
was before.